ingoodcents.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy | In Good Cents

In Good Cents does request information during [giveaways](http://ingoodcents.com/category/giveaways "Giveaways") or surveys, such as your e-mail address. If you [win a giveaway](http://ingoodcents.com/tag/winners "giveaway winner"), additional information is necessary to provide you with your prize(s). Aside from prize winners and when scheduling classes, In Good Cents does not collect information such as your phone number, address, or other private details. I understand that **privacy of your information is very important**.

Information, such as your e-mail address, collected when you comment or ask a question,   is used to answer questions or reply to your comment.   Your e-mail address is only visible by administrators only and can not be seen by other readers.

In addition, In Good Cents is supported by [3rd party advertisers](http://ingoodcents.com/about/policies/disclosure "disclosure policy") which may collect information including your IP address, your ISP, and other information about your browsing capabilities using cookies and/or web beacons. This information is used only to target advertising.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.     Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on visits to this site and other sites on the Internet.     You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "google opt out policy").

In Good Cents collects information to:

  * Improve the site
  * Administer giveaways, contests, promotions, surveys, and other site features
  * To distribute [daily e-mails to subscribers](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=ingoodcents&loc=en_US "subscribe by e-mails")

If you [subscribe to In Good Cents by e-mail](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=ingoodcents&loc=en_US "subscribe by e-mails"), you do opt in to receiving one e-mail per day with a round-up of the latest deals.   These e-mails are sent each day between 5:00 PM and 7:0o PM.   Each e-mail has directions for you to easily unsubscribe, if you choose to do so.   To unsubscribe, please view the links at the bottom of your   most recent e-mail.

As a frugal blog, I often link to offers from third parties or services that are not part of this site.   These parties have separate and independent privacy policies.   Therefore, I have no responsibility or liability for the content or activities of those linked sites.   Nevertheless, I do try hard to only link to reliable and reputable sites to protect the integrity of my own site and me.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

As a website which may receive visitors from the state of California, I must comply with the [California Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.privacy.ca.gov/ "california protection act").

Because I value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
**  
This site is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA ([Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html "children's protection act")). Though this is a family-friendly site that tries hard to only list family-friendly material.   However, like most websites, the material and services on In Good Cents are directed towards audiences that are at least 18 years old and older.   In addition, you must be at least 18 years of age to participate in any giveaways or contests featured on In Good Cents.

By using   this site, you consent to this privacy policy.   If I decide to change the privacy policy, I will update the Privacy Policy modification date below:

_This policy was last modified on February 2, 2011._

For questions regarding this privacy policy, please [contact me](http://ingoodcents.com/about/contact).

_This post may contain affiliate links. When you use them, you support this site. Thank you!  
For more information, please read my [disclosure policy](http://ingoodcents.com/about/policies/disclosure)._
